Track 5.2 Unit 5 Grammar Activity 1
Bài 5.2 Đơn vị 5 Ngữ pháp Bài tập 1
Listen and tick or cross
Nghe và đánh dấu tích hoặc gạch chéo
I love being with my grandma.
Mình rất thích ở cùng bà.
Yesterday she looked after me.
Hôm qua bà trông mình.
I didn't have any homework, so she didn't study with me.
Mình không có bài tập, nên bà không học cùng mình.
But she is good at the piano, so she played the piano with me.
Nhưng bà giỏi chơi piano, nên bà chơi piano cùng mình.
Then in the afternoon she cooked pizza for lunch.
Rồi buổi chiều bà nấu pizza cho bữa trưa.
It was delicious.
Rất ngon.
It was Saturday, so she didn't travel to school by bus with me.
Đó là thứ Bảy, nên bà không đi xe buýt đến trường cùng mình.
But it was hot and sunny, so we cycled to the park.
Nhưng trời nóng và nắng, nên bọn mình đạp xe đến công viên.